{
    "id": "4a2391711d6d4beca6df0aca99ecc94c",
    "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Have you bought …………………… mangoes?",
            "description": "We use any in negative or interrogative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "29a662ec95a243d094ae2eb52d80b31d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you lend me ……………………. money?",
            "description": "Some can be used in questions that express a command or request. ",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4045e8a9a4024a92bd92ec945bafb8d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… seat was taken.",
            "description": "We use a singular noun after every.",
            "answers": [
                "Every",
                "All",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d704001414364fefa76a1df611af89fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Five students are seated on ……………………..",
            "description": "We use each before a singular noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "all bench",
                "each bench",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "136edd42161a4da59c44aafe2b024870"
        },
        {
            "question": "He visits us …………………….. three days.",
            "description": "Every can be used before plural nouns that refer to intervals.",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "each",
                "all"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bbff4c0147d54d88ae8e37342cb97ca2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is not likely to recover. That means there is ………………….. hope of his recovery.",
            "description": "Little means not much.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "087161898e9549fd9d07a2430bc2f558"
        },
        {
            "question": "He showed ……………………….. concern for me.",
            "description": "Little means not much.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "815084a7e3b9413e929218033d3e98b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… tact would have saved the situation.",
            "description": "A little means 'some though not much'.",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "A little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4030a480f4524e3480ae24c8edadf584"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… knowledge is a dangerous thing.",
            "description": "A little means 'some though not much'.",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "A little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "07d9df757a23403dad8f7fbb49b5aa1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. grain we had was damaged in the rains.",
            "description": "The little means not much but all that is there.",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "A little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fa101dd6d1d040dfb37b4e3581ad977d"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… people are so hopeless as drunkards.",
            "description": "Few means hardly any.",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "A few",
                "The few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "973064c6acdd4f67b1ca1143f32bf8ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. remarks that he made were very poignant.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "A few",
                "The few"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "38045ab9452842d5b2e81e37a24534d3"
        }
    ]
}